The place that we saw her for the first time is the relics of Asshai.
At that time, the power of our suppressors was insufficient.
We fell at the door of the relic
She's the one who saved us.
Although not so gentle
The target has been captured
Take him/her away.
Execute the memory erasure program
Hello,everyone.
I'm Xiaofeng.
In this issue, we will get to know Frigg, the eldest sister next door.
When we wake up,
It was already in Sing Tao, and the predators come to attacked.
ShirLi mutated unfortunately in order to protect her brother.
We were commissioned by ZeKe to find Frigg.
But what a coincidence.
She's not in the lab.
We accidentally triggered the system.
She replied: "when you visit, you should at least choose when the host is at home."
"Sorry.
I'm here to deliver a message.
I didn't mean to go through your stuff. "
"stranger, please explain why you are here."
Obviously proudly say that we are strangers
Finally, she gently agreed to the request. Then when we go back to Sing Tao.
Things are out of control.
ZeKe also made a decision.
Obviously he don't like the Heirs of Aida.
But he had to go back for her sister.
Actually, he should know.
What the Sage wants is the key in his hand.
The set of keys
was given to him by his father, Hank
Although I don't know what to do.
But I also acquiesced in their departure.
When we catch up again,
Frigg is already standing there.
Red hair symbolizes the flame and the light of the Heirs of Aida.
Although the body has been transformed into a machine
But it doesn't hinder their inner firmness.
She's here to pick up ZeKe.
Franz also chased here.
00:01:39,030him 00:01:41,570
But we still couldn't keep them.
So we had to set out to the port of Bengis.
It was Praying for Life Festival when I saw her again.
Fireworks was all over the sky in Bengis.
But she had no time to appreciate it and hurried by with ZeKe.
We snuck past.
Unexpectedly, we were discovered.
Stop hiding.
Kid, come out and show your face.
She's still so gentle.
But we had to fight her.
It's obvious
Great disparity in strength
We were defeated.
She didn't kill us.
But let's be polite next time.
I don't hate you.
But next time you ask a question, remember to be polite.
After another long journey, we came to Moby Dick Island.
She stood aloof in front of the merry-go-round.
there is a feeling of not daring to approach.
We tried to help ZeKe, but he refused.
Is he looking down on our strength?
Not really.
He hates us who work for Hykros.
His father was forced to death by Hykros.
The mother also killed herself.
They are not qualified parents.
Leave ZeKe and his sister depend on each other.
After all these years,
Maybe he didn't really trust anyone.
Frigga struck and subdued us with one blow
But she still didn't hurt us.
This woman is supposed to be our enemy.
But let us go again and again.
Thanks to her help on Miyu Island.
But after curing ShirLi, ZeKe left again.
At this point, ZeKe seems to be starting to believe us.
"Thank you.
But after that, I don't want to involve you. "
When we came to Wallan,
I saw her again.
We had just been defeated by Hill.
She saved us again.
And left as aloof as ever.
She really looks like a big sister.
Heared that she loves car racing.
Maybe only speed can make her forget her loneliness.
Heard that she was picked up by the Sage.
On the verge of death
At the time of losing everything
When there is nothing left
Maybe that's why she's so loyal to the Sage.
She must hate the world, too.
The world that took everything away from her.
But when I see her again,
She stood at the top of the mountain
The Sage is not dead.
They're also watching Vera.
But it is clear that their purpose is different from ours.
She seems to want to open up this time.
She said
the Heirs of Aida is also for the good of the world.
Just in an extreme way.
the protagonist seem to understand her.
But I still don't understand why she let the protagonist go again and again.
Is it because the protagonist have nothing?
Is it because the protagonist showed her who she used to be?
No parents.
No relatives.
Even no memory.
But the protagonist wants to help others and save the world on the verge of destruction.
The abyss of disorder is about to be opened.
I hope to see her again.
Frigg, the eldest sister next door
That's all for this issue.
Follow Xiaofeng and experience different tower of fantasy.